binaryoptionstradingitm.com 2018-02-15

# Privacy - Binary Options Trading Signals

**Privacy Policy – BinaryOptionsTradingITM.com**

BinaryOptionsTradingITM.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy on-line. The following statement sets our privacy policy. For the purpose of this Privacy Statement “BinaryOptionsTradingITM.com” shall mean “BinaryOptionsTradingITM.com”. This policy may change from time to time so please re-read this policy periodically.

**What We Gather From You**  
Our site collects information in several ways. When you sign up with our BinaryOptionsTradingITM.com services, you are required to complete an online signup form. BinaryOptionsTradingITM.com request your “Contact Information” like your name and email address.

**Contact Information**  
The Contact Information from the signup form is used to register users in our database, and is also used to get in touch with them when necessary.

**Who Do We Share Your Contact Information With?**  
You should note that the Contact Information you have provided will not be made publicly available, nor sold to third parties. Ever.

BinaryOptionsTradingITM.com may disclose Contact Information in special cases where BinaryOptionsTradingITM.com has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose Contact Information when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes necessary to maintain services and improve our products and services.

**Security**  
Our site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use SSL secure server with digital certificates (https://) and all personal information is fully encrypted during all transactions. Please note, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. As a result, while we attempt to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission we attempt to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems.

**Notification of Changes**  
If at some point in the future, there is a change to our privacy policy that will affect your personal information, we will notify you by email of the relevant changes.

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practises of this site or your dealings with this website, please email our Customer Care Department at info@binaryoptionstradingitm.com
